Henry Allen Moe Papers 1920-1975 Mss.B.M722
American Philosophical Society
- Henry Allen Moe Papers, 1920-1975; 120 lin. feet (Box 1-344)
  - Saturday Children's Theatre
  - Saturday Evening Post
  - Sauer, Carl O
  - Sauer, Mrs. Carl O
  - Sauer, Jonathan
  - Saunders, Betsy I
  - Saunders, George A
  - Saunders, W. B., Company
  - Savage, Abe L
  - Savage, Eugene
  - Sawtelle, Alvin C
  - Sawtelle, Mrs. Virginia
  - Sawyer, Philip
  - Sawyer, Ralph A
  - Sayles, G O
  - Saylor, Henry H
  - Scammon, Howard
  - Scarritt, Horace S
  - Scattergood, Alfred G
  - Schaefer, Walter Vincent
  - Schaeffer, Adalberto
  - Schaetzel, J Robert
  - Schaffner, Joseph Halle
  - Schairer, Gerda
  - Schapiro, Meyer
  - Schatzman, Frederick A
  - Scheie, Harold C
  - Schelling, George
  - Schenck, Mrs. Edgar Craig
  - Scherer, Margaret H
  - Scherer, Paul A
  - Scheuer, James
  - Scheuer, James H
  - Schindler, Dali
  - Schlatter, Richard
  - Schlesinger, Arthur,Jr.
  - Schlesinger, Robert M
  - Schlesinger, Stephen L
  - Schmitt, Mrs. Bernadotte
  - Schmitt, Francis O
  - Schnebelen, Pierre
  - Schneider, Herbert Wallace
  - Schnitzer, Robert C
  - Schomburg, A A
  - Schonthal, Ruth
  - Schoonmaker, Frank, & Company
  - Schrader, Mrs. Emagene
  - Schrader, Richard M
  - Schreiner, Ernst J
  - Schulte's Book Store
  - Schultz, T W
  - Schulz, William F
  - Schuman, William
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine
  - Schurz, William L
  - Schuster, M Lincoln
  - Schutz, E F
  - Schuyler, Robert Livingston
  - Schwamm, Harvey L
  - Schwartz, Benjamin
  - Schwarzschild, Leopold
  - Schwenkmeyer, Barry
  - Science
  - Science Service
  - Science Service - Simpson, Richard M
  - Scott, David W
  - Scott, Jonathan F
  - Scott, Russell
  - Scott, Mrs. Ruth Ford
  - Scribner, Harold
  - Scribner Book Store
  - Scriven Foundation, Inc.
    - Annual meeting
    - Annual report
    - Committee on Grants
    - Estimated income and disbursements
    - Minutes, Scholarship information
    - Scholarships
    - Special meeting
    - Thirty-Fourth Annual Report
    - To the Board of Directors
  - Scudder, Hervey C
  - Scully, Dorothy W
  - Scully, Robert E
  - Seaborg, Glenn T
  - Seabury, Arthur
  - Seamon, Nancy E
  - Sears, Mrs. John
  - Sears, Paul B
  - Sears Roebuck & Company
  - Sedgwick, Ellery
  - Seeger, Charles
  - Seibert, Deni
  - Seidenberg, Roderick
  - Seifert, Donald
  - Seiffert, Herman
  - Seitz, Frederick
  - Selden Society
  - Sellers, Ashley
  - Sellers, Charles Coleman
  - Sellin, David
  - Sen, D K
  - Senior, John
  - Senior, John L
  - Senior, Mrs. Maud C
  - Sepeshy, Zoltan
  - Serebrier, José
  - Serra-Badué, Daniel
  - Setton, Kenneth S
  - Severinghaus, Aura E
  - Seymour, Catryra
  - Seymour, Whitney North
  - Shackleton, Robert
  - Shacklock, Floyd
  - Shafer, Paul D
  - Shakespeare Anniversary Committee
  - Shali, M B
  - Shanet, Howard
  - Shank, Donald J
  - Shankland, Mrs. Alice
  - Shannon, Fred A
  - Shapley, Harlow
  - The Shapley School
  - Shappert, F W
  - Sharp, Geraldine
  - Sharpe, William
  - Shaver, Dorothy
  - Shaw, Alejandro
  - Shaw, Ferdon
  - Shaw, Robert Alfred
  - Sheaffer, Louis
  - Shears, Helen M
  - Shefelman, Harold S
  - Shelley, Edwin F
  - Shepard, David A
  - Shepard, Marianna
  - Shepardson, Whitney H
  - Sheperd, Howard C
  - Sherburne, E G, Jr.
  - Sheridan, Judson
  - Sherman, Annette
  - Sherman, Connecticut
  - Sherman, Lester S
  - Sherman, R
  - Sherman, Rose
  - Sherman Sentinel
  - Shields, Paul O
  - Shipstead, Henrik
  - Shipton, Clifford K
  - Shlichter, Sumner H
  - Shoemaker, Neille
  - Shoemaker, William S
  - Shope, Richard Edwin
  - Shorter, William J
  - Shotwell, James T
  - Shrader, Stephen
  - Shriver, Sargent
  - Shryock, Richard Harrison
  - Shugg, Roger W
  - Shull, George H
  - Shuman, Bertram A
  - Sibbett, Morgan
  - Sigmon, Carl
  - Sikes, W E
  - Silber, John R
  - Silberschmidt, Carl
  - Silva, Irma Salas
  - Silver, Samuel
  - Silvette, Herbert
  - Simeti, Mary Beardon
  - Simon, Sir Francis
  - Simon, Louis
  - Simoncic, Klement
  - Simoni, S
  - Simons, Hans
  - Simonson, Lee
  - Simpson, Carl
  - Simpson, Lesley Byrd
  - Simpson, Lewis P
  - Sinclair, Gregg M
  - Sison, George F
  - Siudy, Goerge S, Jr.
  - Sixth Annual Festival of American Folklife
  - Sizer, Theodore
  - Skafte-Lindblom, Saga
  - Skeel, H R
  - Skeel, Mrs. H R
  - Skouras, Mrs. Spyros P
  - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture
  - Slater, Joseph E
  - Sleepy Hollow Restorations
  - Slichter, Sumner H
  - Sloane, Alfred P., Foundation
  - Sloane, W. & J.
  - Slobodkin, Louis
  - Sluiter, Engle
  - Sly, Allan
  - Smart, George K
  - Smit, Leo
  - Smith, Allan
  - Smith, Beverly
  - Smith, Mrs. Beverly
  - Smith, C Paul
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague
  - Smith, Cassandra
  - Smith, Mrs. Chloetheil Woodard
  - Smith, Courtney
  - Smith, Cyril Stanley
  - Smith, Datus C
  - Smith, David
  - Smith, David Nichol
  - Smith, E A Cappelen
  - Smith, Emil
  - Smith, G E Kidder
  - Smith, Geoffrey S
  - Smith, George B
  - Smith, George William
  - Smith, Henry C
  - Smith, H R W
  - Smith, Irwin
  - Smith, James Kellum
  - Smith, Mrs. Joan
  - Smith, Mrs. Katharine Dennis
  - Smith, Kellogg
  - Smith, Ken
  - Smith, Mrs. Louise
  - Smith, Myron Bement
  - Smith, Ray W
  - Smith, Robert C
  - Smith, Ruth Alice
  - Smith, William G
  - Smithsonian Conferences on Museums and Education
  - Smithsonian Institution
  - Smithsonian Museums' Conference
  - Smokers' problems
  - Smyth, Charles and Emily
  - Smyth, Craig Hugh
  - Snyder, Margaret
  - Sobel, Eli
  - Sobel, Norman T
  - Soby, James Thrall
  - Social Science Research Council
    - Agenda for the meeting of the Board of directors
    - Board of directors. Minutes
    - Committee on problems and policy Minutes
    - Committee on review of Fellowship policy
    - Financial report
    - Impact of the war on American society
    - A research memorandum on internal migration resulting from the war effort
  - Social Security administration
  - Society for the promotion of Roman studies
  - Society of Friends. Council on education
  - Sockman, Ralph W
  - Solberg, Carl
  - Soltero, Donald E
  - Soltero, Donald J, Jr.
  - Sonnenberg, Benjamin
  - Soriano, Santos
  - Soundings
  - Southern Illinois University
  - Southern Illinois University. Proposal for a centre of Soviet and East European studies Press
  - Southwell, R V
  - Spaatz, Carl
  - Spaeth, Carl
  - Spahr, Walter E
  - Spalding, H N
  - Spalding, Mrs. H N
  - Spargo, John W
  - Speight, Francis
  - Speiser, E A
  - Spencer, John
  - Sperry, W L
  - Spies, Tom D
  - Spicer, Edward
  - Spilhaus, Athelstan F
  - Spinden, Herbert J
  - Spingarn, Arthur B
  - Spink and Gaborc, Inc.
  - Spoehr, Alexander
  - Sprague, Ver Lynn M
  - Spreen, Charles H
  - Springer, Herman
  - Sproul, Allan
  - Sproul, Kathleen
  - Sproul, Robert Gorden
  - Spruill, Corydon P
  - Spurr, Stephen H
  - Squadron, Howard M
  - Squier, George O
  - Stack, Chris
  - Stack, Edward W
  - Stackpole, Edward
  - Stahl, Edward C M
  - Stakman, E C
  - Stalland, K D
  - Stallings, Laurence
  - Stallings, Sylvia Poteat
  - Stallybrass, W T S
  - Stanislawski, Dan
  - Stanley, Edward
  - Stanley, Pauline G
  - Stanley, Wendell M
  - Stanley, William Schuman
  - Stannard, S R
  - Stanton, Frank
  - Stanton, Madeline
  - Stark, Suzanne
  - Starr, Louis M
  - Stassen, Harold
  - State of Connecticut: Department of Environmental Protection
  - State University of New York at Buffalo
  - Statler-Hilton Hotel
  - Staudinger, Hans
  - Stavig, Lawrence M
  - Stearns, Mrs. Marshall Winslow
  - Stechert, G. E., & Company
  - Stedman, Alfred D
  - Stedman, Bruce
  - Steefel, Lawrence D
  - Steele, Winthrop
  - Steere, William Campbell
  - Steeves, Willard
  - Stegner, Wallace
  - Steichen dinner
  - Steichen, Edward
  - Steichen, Kate
  - Stein, Oswald
  - Steiner, Oscar H
  - Steiner, Ralph
  - Steinhardt, Samuel C
  - Steinway, Theodore
  - Stephens, John C
  - Sterling, Nicholas J
  - Stern, Alfred K
  - Stern, Curt
  - Stern, Gerd
  - Stern, H Peter
  - Stern, J David
  - Sternberg, Vernon
  - Sternberg, Mrs. Vernon
  - Stetson, Eugene W
  - Stevens, David H
  - Stevens, George M
  - Stevens, John F
  - Stevenson, Adlai
  - Stevenson, Earl P
  - Stevenson, Elizabeth
  - Stevenson, Gordon
  - Stevenson, William E
  - Stewart, Cynthia
  - Stewart, Fred W
  - Stewart, Irvin
  - Stewart, Milo
  - Stiles, James E
  - Stimson, Henry L
  - Stirton, Murray
  - Stocker, W N
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps
  - Stokes, Donald E
  - Stokes, H G
  - Stokes, Robert W
  - Stone, Candace
  - Stone, Mrs. Emily
  - Stone, Ferdinand
  - Stone, George Winchester
  - Stone, Marshall
  - Stony Brook School
  - Story and the Story Press
  - Stott, Gilmore
  - Stout, A B
  - Stout, Wesley Winans
  - Stratton, Julius A
  - Straus, Herbert R
  - Straus, Jack I
  - Straus, Roger Williams, Jr.
  - Strauss, Lewis L
  - Strausz-Hope, Robert
  - Strawbridge, Robert E, Jr.
  - Streeter, Frank S
  - Streit, G K
  - Strickland, Frank
  - Strickland, William
  - Stricks, Joseph
  - Stringfield, Lamar
  - Strode-V, Arnold
  - Stromgren, Bengt
  - Stroud, Joan
  - Stroud, Mrs. W B Dixon
  - Stryker, Roy E
  - Stuart, Jesse
  - Stuart, Meriwether
  - Stubbs, W B
  - Studeny, Mrs. Janice
  - Studin, Charles H
  - Stumpf, Mark P
  - Suddarth, Mrs. Jane
  - Suddarth, Thomas H, Jr.
  - Sudduth, William Henry
  - Suffolk Museum at Stony Brook
  - Sugiura, Masahisa
  - Suits, Chauncey Guy
  - Sullivan, Harry Stack
  - Sullivan, Mary
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays
  - Sulzberger, Mrs. Iphigena Ochs
  - Sulzberger-Rolfe
  - Superintendent of Documents
  - Surrey, Stanley
  - Sutherland, Arthur
  - Sutton, Ione Ulrich
  - Sutton, Joseph G
  - Svenson, Ed
  - Svenson, Henry K
  - Svirsky, Leon
  - Swann, W F
  - Swanzey, Eugene F
  - Swarthmore College
  - Swartz, Louis Herbert
  - Swayduck, Edward
  - Sweeney, James Johnson
  - Sweeney, Seán
  - Sweeney, Valerie and Seán
  - Sweeting, Elizabeth
  - Swift, Harold
  - Swindler, William F
  - Swing, John Temple
  - Switz, Theodore Mac Lean
  - Switzer, Mary E
  - Swoboda, Henry
  - Swords, Gerard S
  - Syme, Sir Ronald
  - Symington, Cecily
  - Symington, Charles
  - Syrett, Harold C
  - Szasz, Suzanne
  - Szigeti, Joseph
  - Szoverffy, Joseph
  - Taeni, John I
  - Tait, Marion
  - Talbot, K H
  - Talbot, Phillips
  - Taliaferro, Lucy G
  - Taliaferro, William Hay
  - Talk before concerned citizens for the Arts
  - Tallet, Jorge
  - Tameirao, Mrs. Helena Ravese
  - Tanaka, Mrs. Kotaro
  - Tanis, Gilbert R
  - Tannenbaum, Frank
  - Tannenbaum, Libby
  - Tannenbaum, S
  - Taplin, Frank E
  - Tarr, Curtis
  - Tatler Magazine
  - Taubes, Frederic
  - Taubman, Howard
  - Taylor, Frank A
  - Taylor, G O
  - Taylor, Sir Hugh
  - Taylor, Mrs. Kay
  - Taylor, Mrs. Lisa
  - Taylor, Mrs. Morgan
  - Taylor, O A
  - Taylor, Mrs. Pamela
  - Taylor, Paul
  - Taylor, T W J
  - Tead, Ordway
  - Ten Eyck, Barent
  - Tenney, Charles D
  - Terrell, Carroll F
  - Tewksbury, Donald G
  - Thacher, John Boyd, II
  - Thane, Alexander, Jr.
  - Theimer, Ernst T
  - Theras, Nicki
  - Thiel College
  - Thiele, Albert
  - Thiesen, John
  - Thin, D Ainslie
  - Thin, James
  - Thiron, J
  - Thoene, Fred A
  - Thom, Arthur
  - Thomas, Byron
  - Thomas, E Donnell
  - Thomas, Lowell
  - Thomas, Minor Wine
  - Thompson, Mrs. Frances
  - Thompson, Frank
  - Thompson, Homer A
  - Thompson, J Eric S
  - Thompson, Kenneth W
  - Thompson, Lyman
  - Thompson, Margaret
  - Thompson, Mary S
  - Thompson, Ruth L
  - Thompson, W Fawcett
  - Thomson, Charles A
  - Thomson, David Cleghorn
  - Thomson, Elizabeth H
  - Thomson, Frank B
  - Thonssen, Lester
  - Thorndike, Lynn
  - Thorne, Francis
  - Thorne, Landon K
  - Thorne, Samuel E
  - Thrasher, Frederic M
  - Thurdman, Mrs. Sue M
  - Thwing, Charles F
  - Tiffany, Louis Comfort, Foundation
  - Tiffany, Investment Advisory Account
  - Tikal, Guatemala
  - Tikofsky, Ronald S
  - Tillinghast, Charles C
  - Time Capsule Committee
  - Tinbergen, Niko
  - Tindale, Richard T
  - Tiselius, Arne W K
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Company
  - Toksvig, Signe
  - Tourtellot, Arthur B
  - Towart, Sanford K
  - Tracy, William J
  - Trade Union Women of African Heritage, Inc.
  - Train(?), Charles E
  - Trautman, Ray L
  - Tremaine, C M
  - Trenham, N Bradford
  - Tresselt, L W
  - Trippett, Byron K
  - Trout, Allan M
  - Trowbridge, Buell
  - Trueblood, Edward G
  - Truesdell, C
  - Tsakpenoglu, Pandelis Y
  - Tucker, Allen
  - Tucker, Allen, Memorial Foundation
  - Tucker, E R
  - Tukey, John W
  - Tuker, Mrs. Eufrasia A W
  - Turkel, Victor
  - Turlington, Edgar
  - Turner, Evan H
  - Turner, Horatio W
  - Turner, Thomas B
  - Tuttle, Charles F
  - Tuttle, H Emerson
  - Tuve, Merle A
  - Tyler, E F
  - Tyler, Mrs. Hilda B
  - Tylor, T H
  - Ubell, Earl
  - Uhler, Alfred M
  - Uhler, Kathleen
  - Ulam, Adam B
  - Unbegaun, Boris
  - Underwood, Dixon
  - Underwood, Thomas I
  - Union Theological Seminary
  - United States Armed Forces Institute
  - U. S. Civil Service Commission
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture
  - U. S. Department of State
  - U. S. Embassy of Argentina
  - U. S. Government Printing Office
  - U. S. House of Representatives
  - U. S. Immigration and naturalization service
  - U. S. Lines
  - U. S. Navy Department
  - U. S. Tax exempt foundations
  - U. S. Naval Academy
  - U. S. Passport Agency
  - U. S. Public Health Service
  - U. S. Taxation of foundations
  - U. S. Treasury Advisory Committee
  - U. S. Treasury Department
  - University Dept. of Romance Languages and Literature
  - University extension division, Chapel Hill
  - University of Chicago
  - University of Cincinnati
  - University of Connecticut
  - University of Denver
  - University of Dublin Fund
  - University of Dundee
  - University of Florida
  - University of Hartford
  - University of Illinois
  - University of London
  - University of Oklahoma Press
  - University of Oxford
  - University of Oxford - Queen's College
  - University of Pennsylvania
  - University of Texas
  - University Resident Theatre Association
  - Unknown: Book manuscript...
  - Unknowns
  - Unterecker, John
  - Upjohn, Mrs. Everard M
  - Usui, B
  - Utley, Grant
  - Vaillant, George C
  - Vaillant, Susan
  - Valentine, Alan
  - Valentine, Willard L
  - Vallance, William Roy
  - Van Alstine, D Leonhard
  - Van Camp, Ruth
  - Van der Poel, Susan
  - Vanderpump, G J
  - Vandiver, Frank E
  - Van Doren, Irita
  - Van Doren, Mark
  - Van Dusen, Henry Pitney
  - Van Dyke, Willard
  - Van Heyningen, W E
  - Van Lerdeu, Karin
  - Van Nostrand, N W
  - Van Ravensway, Charles
  - Van Veen, Stuyvesant
  - Van Vleck, John H
  - Van Wagenen, Jared
  - Van Wagenen, Margaret
  - Vargas, Luis
  - Vasques, Gregorio T
  - Vaughan, Alden T
  - Vaughn, William
  - Veale, Sir Douglas
  - Velasquez, Carmen Comacho
  - Velasquez, Julieta C
  - Velez, Ismael
  - Venegas, Carmen
  - Verdery, Francis de Luze
  - Verdery, John D
  - Verdery, Marion Jackson
  - Verdery, Patrick
  - Verdery, Richard J
  - Verdery, Richard N
  - Verdery, Rosamond
  - Verdery, Susan
  - Vermeale, Carmelin
  - Vernadsky, George
  - Verne, Miss
  - Ver Steeg, Clarence L
  - Veterans Relief Organization
  - Vetlesen Fund - Photographs
  - Vetlesen Prize
  - Vickery, H B
  - Vickery, Charles V
  - Villa Bencista
  - Villa Serbelloni
  - Village Haven
  - Villegas, Daniel Cosío
  - Virginia Museum of the Fine Arts
  - Visual Arts Projects Panel
  - Vita
  - Vlastos, Gregory
  - Vogt, William
  - Volkmer, Jean
  - Volpe, Alfred E
  - Von Karman, Theodore
  - Von Trott, Adam
  - Voorhees, E N
  - Vosburgh, Harry S
  - Voucher for purchases
  - Vouchers claiming payment by U.S.
  - Vouchers paid by U.S.
  - Voynich, E L
  - Vreeland, Diana
  - Wade, R H B
  - Wade, Winthrop H
  - Wadleigh, Richard
  - Wadsworth, Frank W
  - Wadsworth, Philip A
  - Waggoner, Alvin
  - Wagley, Charles
  - Wagley, Philip F
  - Wagner, Fred T
  - Wagner, H R
  - Wagner, Max L
  - Wagner, Richard
  - Wagner, Robert F
  - Wagner & Company
  - Wagoner, Walter G
  - Wakeman, Chesed
  - Walcott, Frederic C
  - Walcott, Gregory Dexter
  - Walcott, Mrs. Helen
  - Waldock, Sir Humphrey
  - Walke, Mrs. Frank Anthony
  - Walker, Challis
  - Walker, G E
  - Walker, Hudson D
  - Walker, John
  - Walker, Legh
  - Walker, Maynard
  - Walker, Ralph
  - Walker, Wyndham L
  - Wallace, De Witt
  - Wallace, George B
  - Wallace, John C
  - Wallace, Mrs. Ruth B
  - Wallace, Schuyler C
  - Wallach, Marshall
  - Wallen, Saul
  - Waller, George M
  - Wallis, W Allen
  - Walsh, Dorothy G
  - Walsh, Raymond J
  - Walsh, Richard J
  - Walt, Norman E, Jr.
  - Walter H. Baker Company
  - Walter, Henry G, Jr.
  - Walton, Guy
  - Wanamaker, Pearl A
  - Wang, Arthur W
  - Wangerin, R H
  - Ward, Archibald
  - Ward, Clarence
  - Ward, E H P
  - Ward, J A C
  - Ward, J D
  - Ward, Judson C
  - Ward, Paul L
  - Ward, Robert
  - Ward, Stetson
  - Ward, William
  - Warde, Frederic
  - Wardwell, Allen
  - Warner, Frank
  - Warner, W Lloyd
  - Warner, William S
  - Warren, Dorothy
  - Warren, Louis B
  - Warren, William C
  - Warshaw, Mrs. Augusta
  - Warwick, Maud E., Fund
  - Washburn, Gordon
  - Washburn, S L
  - Washington, S Walter
  - Washington Gallery of Modern Art
  - Washington University
  - Wasson, R Gordon
  - Waters, Eleanor C
  - Watkins, Franklin C
  - Watkins, Mrs. Ida
  - Watkins, Mrs. Mary B
  - Watson, Colin
  - Watson, Thomas J
  - Watt, John N
  - Watts, Robert B
  - Watts, Mrs. Robert
  - Watts, Van
  - Waugh, Sidney
  - Waverly Press, Inc.
  - Weaver, Warren
  - Webb, Mrs. Sally
  - Weber, Ernest
  - Webster, Betuel M
  - Webster, Bruce
  - Webster, Samuel C
  - Wechsler, Louis K
  - Weed, Le Roy J
  - Weeks, Edward
  - Weigand, Hermann J
  - Weigl, Mrs. Vally
  - Weihman, Clifford T
  - Weil, André
  - Weil, Stephen E
  - Weismiller, Edward R
  - Weiss, Marion
  - Weiss, Paul A
  - Weizmann, Chaim, Centenary Celebration
  - Welch, William Henry
  - Weldman, Muriel P
  - Welling, Richard
  - Wellman, Harvey R
  - Welsh, Jane
  - Wells, John A
  - Welsh, Peter C
  - Wendel, Hugo C M
  - Wendell, Clare
  - Wentworth, Mrs. Elizabeth
  - Wentworth, Howland
  - Weppler, B Joel
  - Wesleyan University
    - Alumni address
    - Board of Trustees
    - Committee on Tenure
    - Facilities committee
    - Memorandum to Administrative Staff
    - Minutes
    - Minutes of Board of Trustees
    - Report of a fund raising survey
    - 12 percent return report
  - Westchester Community College
  - Westchester Service Corporation
  - Westergard, Waldemar
  - Western Behavioral Science Institute
  - Western Union
  - Weston, Harold
  - Wetmore, Alexander
  - Wetmore, Mrs. Alexander
  - Weyer, Edward M
  - Weyl, Hermann
  - Whalen, George
  - Whalen, Grover A
  - Wharton, Dolores D
  - Wheeler, Albert E
  - Wheeler, Alice
  - Wheeler, John Archibald
  - Wheeler, Monroe
  - Wheelwright, Mary C
  - Whelpley, Medley G B
  - Whipple, Allen O
  - Whitaker, R F
  - White Flower Farm
  - White, Gilbert F
  - White, Harvey E
  - White, John F
  - White, Lawrence
  - White, Leonard D
  - White, Lynn
  - White, Morton
  - White, William A., & Sons
  - White, William Crawford
  - Whitehead, A Pennington
  - Whitehill, Walter Muir
  - Whitelaw, Robert H
  - Whitelaw, Robert N S
  - Whiting, F A
  - Whitmack, Ann
  - Whitnall, Ruth
  - Whitney, Frances
  - Whitney, John Hay
  - Whitridge, Worthington
  - Whittaker, James
  - Whittemore, Thomas C
  - Who's Who Among Authors and Journalists, etc.
  - Wicker, Cyrus French
  - Widseth, Mrs. Janet
  - Wiener, Frederick Bernays
  - Wiener, Paul
  - Wiener, Mrs. Paul
  - Wiesner, Jerome B
  - Wiggins, James Russell
  - Wilberforce, Robert
  - Wilbur, Mary Tyler
  - Wilcox, J Taney
  - Wilcox, Samuel
  - Wildenhain, Frans
  - Wilder, Mitchell A
  - Wilder, Philip S
  - Wilder, Robert G
  - Wilder, Thornton
  - Wilding-White, Henry
  - Wildman, Frederick S
  - Wiley, Bell I
  - Wilk, Jacob
  - Wilkinson, Maxwell P
  - Wilkinson, R J
  - Wilks, Samuel S
  - Wilks, Mrs. Samuel S
  - Will, John M
  - Willen, Mrs. Pearl L
  - Willetts, Eliza L
  - Willets, Morris Legget
  - William Morrow and Company
  - Williams, Arthur
  - Williams, Bayard
  - Williams, Blair S
  - Williams, E T
  - Williams, Flora
  - Williams, John Page
  - Williams, Margaret J
  - Williams, Molli Scott
  - Williams, Ursula Scott
  - Williams, Mrs. William Robert
  - Williamson, W Rulon and Carolee
  - Willits, Joseph H
  - Willoughby, Alfred
  - Wilson & Hanna
  - Wilson, A G
  - Wilson, Arthur
  - Wilson, Carol A
  - Wilson, Carroll L
  - Wilson, E Bright, Jr.
  - Wilson, Edwin Bidwell
  - Wilson, Hunt
  - Wilson, J K
  - Wilson, James Q
  - Wilson, John
  - Wilson, John A
  - Wilson, Mrs. Julius Lane
  - Wilson, Kenneth G
  - Wilson, Mrs. Mazie
  - Wilson, O Meredith
  - Wilson, P L
  - Wilson, Thomas J
  - Wilson, Walter
  - Wilson, Mrs. Walter
  - Wilson, Woodrow, recollection of, by Raymond B. Fosdick
  - Wiltwyck School
  - Winchell, Benjamin LaFon
  - Winchell, Mrs. Elizabeth W
  - Winchester, Marchioness of
  - Wine lists
  - Wines
  - Wing, James, Jr.
  - Wing, Raymond
  - Winlock, H E
  - Winsand, Orville
  - Winslow, C -E A
  - Winslow, Carlile P
  - Winslow, Edmund J
  - Winslow, Mary N
  - Winslow, Richard S
  - Winternitz, Emanuel
  - Wintersteen, Mrs. John
  - Winthrop, Stimson, Putnam and Roberts
  - Wisdom Hall of Fame
  - Wise, Blanche
  - Wise, C R
  - Wissler, Clark
  - Witter, Dean, Jr.
  - Witter, John
  - Witter, Mrs. John
  - Witter, Peter
  - WNET-TV
  - Wodlinger, David
  - Wolf, Howard
  - Wolfe, Bertram D
  - Wolfe, Paul
  - Wolfenden, J H
  - Wolfle, Dael
  - Wood, Allen H, III
  - Wood, Barry
  - Wood, L Hollingsworth
  - Wood, Lester
  - Wood, P G
  - Wood, W
  - Wood, Walter A
  - Woodbridge, Frederick J E
  - Woodd-Cahusac, S A
  - Woodmere Academy
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation
  - Woods, Katherine
  - Woodward, C Vann
  - Woodward Report. Yale Alumnus
  - Woodworth, G Wallace
  - Woolfendon, William E
  - Wooster School
  - World Workshop Library on Humor
  - Worthington, Mrs. Margaret
  - Wriggins, Mrs. W Howard
  - Wright, Andrew
  - Wright, Christopher
  - Wright, David G
  - Wright, E H
  - Wright, Mrs. Eloise Smith
  - Wright, Ernest B
  - Wright, Mrs. Frank Lloyd
  - Wright, Louis B
  - Wright, Sydney L
  - Wright, Mrs. Sydney L
  - Wyanski, Richard
  - Wyckoff Association in America
  - Wyckoff House Foundation
  - Wyeth, M S
  - Wylie, Sir Francis
  - Wylie, J I
  - Wylie, Lady Kathleen
  - Wylie, Robert H
  - Xavier, Sister Francis
  - Xedes, George
  - Yale University
  - Yale University Press
  - Yalman, Ahmed Emin
  - Yardley, David C M
  - Yeager, A F
  - Yedes, George
  - Yen, Y C James
  - Yerkes, Robert M
  - Ylvisaker, J Wilhelm
  - Yntema, Hessel E
  - Yntema, Theodore O
  - Yoder, Paul E
  - York, Mrs. Edward P
  - Yorker Program
  - Yoshinaga, Amy
  - Young, Arthur N
  - Young, Donald
  - Young, Douglas E
  - Young, Herrick B
  - Young, Mahonri Sharp
  - Young, Philip
  - Young, Robert R
  - Young, Stanley
  - Young, Virginia Brady
  - Young Men's Christian Association
  - Youritzin, Mrs. Gienda Green
  - Youthful mood of patriotism
  - Yuan, Luke C L
  - Yurchenko, Henrietta
  - Z, G
  - Zabel, Morton Dauwen
  - Zabriskie, George
  - Zacher, G H
  - Zahn, Mrs. Adreana R
  - Zajac, Jack
  - Zakar, Sari
  - Zamora, Juan Clemente
  - Zavala, Lauro José
  - Zeek, Mark C
  - Zellers, John A
  - Zettl, Joseph H
  - Ziegler, Edward
  - Zigrosser, Carl
  - Zimmerman, B W
  - Zimmerman, Charles J
  - Zink, Harold
  - Zinsser, Hans
  - Zobell, Claude
  - Zorach, William
  - Zucker, Jacques